Rahul?
- There seems to be some misunderstanding.
- Come.
This packet does not belong to…
We will talk. Get in the car.
What… what is happening here?
Officer, please, please, please.
Let me explain you this.
The car was mine,
but the packet was not mine.
Hey! Why? Why can't you…
- Let me make a call.
- No calls.
Calm down!
- Let… let me make a call, please.
- No call.
Why don't you listen to me?
Enough! Don't irritate me.
Where are you taking her?
Where are you taking me?
Shut up!
Hey, are you listening to me?
Where are we going?
Shut up!
Telling you right now,
stop the fucking car!
This is the desert.
What are we doing here?
We're doing the right thing.
Officer, will you explain me?
Shut up!
There is simply nothing around me.
Stop the car.
Hey, man! Watch it!
My batch has been assigned
to serve the delegates.
But why are you complaining?
Have fun in the 5-star hotel for five days
and then you can catch the smugglers.
It's not like smuggling is going to
stop at this airport, right? Shake on it.
- Hello.
- Arjun dear.
Govind, I have something urgent.
Our COIN officer
managed to separate Priya from Rahul
and put her on a flight to Mumbai.
And made sure that Rahul could not
get in touch with anyone for a few hours.
For you.
Officer, what are we doing here?
This is a completely deserted area.
The place I am taking you to,
you will like it. Shut up!
Can I call my uncle, please?
Listen, Officer, this can escalate
to the higher, higher, higher authorities.
Silent!
I'm telling you this right now.
You don't want to mess with me.
Shut up!
Enough, Enough. Don't irritate me.
Let us take him out of reach…
I'll show you.
- Why did you stop here?
- Come.
- Why did you stop?
- Just get down. Go!
Officer! Officer!
Fuck!
Arbab, connect to the police station
in 10 minutes.
Please.
- What about the consignment?
- Don't worry about that.
Yes, Suresh is handling that.
Please come to the police station. Hurry.
Okay.
Gentlemen, excuse me.
- Sure. Sure.
- Inshallah, Inshallah.
Fuck!
- Sir, is mine done?
- Just a sec. You may go.
- Mr. and Mrs. Sharma.
- Yes, sir.
Here. Your tickets.
After clearing check-in
and security check,
you will go into the washroom,
next to duty-free.
Our janitors will meet you
in your respective washrooms,
who will give you two packets each
after seeing your boarding passes.
We have also booked wheelchairs for you.
So you'll be the first to board the plane.
- Okay.
- Is it clear?
Just hold on. He's here.
Let me talk to him and figure out.
Yes, just hold.
- Assalam-alaikum.
- Walaikum-assalam.
I've tried everywhere to find a clue.
But can't find as to who took them.
- Please help me find out.
- Wait. Wait here.
Yes, now tell me.
My team was handling the delegates'
protocol on the day of conference.
And everything was going on
as I had intended and as per my plan.
- Yes.
- Tell me. Any news?
No, Arbab has gone inside to find out.
- Okay. Do call me when you figure out.
- Sure.
Good morning, ladies and gentlemen,
this is your captain from the flight deck.
We are now ready
to depart from Milan to Mumbai.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we have now reached our cruising altitude.
Seatbelt signs are now off,
however for your safety,
please keep your belts securely fastened.
You may now use your electronic devices.
We'll be coming to the cabin shortly
with our in-flight service.
Sit back and relax and enjoy the flight.
We are ready to fly.
Caught you.
Where are you running?
Go! Go, go with Mumma. Go!
Darling…
- Are you hungry, my love?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Okay. All right.
Keep me posted, every second. Absolutely.
Every bit of news. Yeah.
Of course. All well. Okay, fine.
- Cheers!
- All is under control.
- Something is bothering me, Sharma ji.
- What? All is calm and quiet.
A little too calm, isn't it?
There's nothing like that.
You're just overthinking.
Let me get some ice.
Nobody is giving me any answers.
Nobody is saying anything.
- Don't worry.
- How will we find out?
Don't worry. It'll work out.
Have faith in the Lord.
I do have faith, Arbab sahib.
But we need to find out.
He… he's here too.
What happened, Anna? Any news?
This is the fourth police station.
No news.
Arbab involved Omar sahib.
- Has the consignment left?
- Yes.
Flights will start landing in Mumbai soon.
- Sir.
- Pen?
- Goodnight.
- All right, sir.
- Mention the time.
- Sure, sir.
Here. In this column.
The flights will land soon, Patel sahib.
- All well?
- Yes, Ramesh bhai.
Our team is batting. Hang up.
Patel sir, Prakash sir is calling you.
I mean, he has called all of you, sir.
Shall we?
Let's go.
- Sir.
Please.
We are about to launch an op today,
called Operation Longshot.
We have specific intel
that Choudhary Syndicate is sending
huge quantities
of drugs and gold to Mumbai.
And a large consignment of luxury goods
is also coming on the Milan flight.
We also have intel that more than
50 couriers are going to land here today.
So all of you have to be super alert.
Especially the officers who'll be in line.
Team, I want this op
to be a grand success.
Arjun Meena will lead the operation.
Arjun, all yours.
Sir.
Wrist watch?
This bag will be kept
in Prakash sir's cabin.
In case of emergency,
you can use the landline in there.
Based on intel
we'll be targeting 19 flights
in the window of three and a half hours.
But we have a situation.
The last flight
from Middle East will take off
half an hour
after the first flight lands here.
So we have to let the first courier
pass through the green channel.
One of our teams along with DRI officers
will follow them and arrest them
as soon as they get orders.
Sajjad and Awasthi will be in that team.
The team will be led by you, Patel sir.
- Mitali,
- Yes, sir.
- Shreelata, Dhuria…
…will be at the domestic airport
because nine
of the 19 flights will land there.
You will detain the passengers sitting
on the seat numbers marked in the list
and get the gold from them.
- Is it clear?
- Yes, sir.
Gold in domestic flights?
Let's go.
Meena!
Do you and Prakash sir think that you guys
are the only honest officers here?
And the rest of us are hand in glove
with the smugglers?
No, Patel sahib.
I have full faith in your honesty.
- 555039, descend, maintain level 980.
- Sir, maintaining 980 for 555039.
For left heading 300 report on localizer.
Ladies and Gentlemen, welcome aboard
the flight from Lucknow to Mumbai.
Our flight time is expected
to be two hours and ten minutes.
Thank you and have a comfortable flight.
Vincent, you will be in line.
And the rest will accompany me
to the arrival hall and green channel.
Right.
Sir. Sir, what does hand in glove mean?
Mitali.
Can you explain this kid
what hand in glove means?
Come on.
Follow me, guys.
Eighteen flights are in the air,
only one to go.
Get the photos of the passengers.
Can you swear on your kid
that you've never been hand in glove?
You know, Mr. Ravi,
a government officer is as honest
or corrupt as his boss.
- You are right, ma'am.
- Come on.
Let's go.
- Dhuria.
- Yes, ma'am.
You wanted to know about hand in glove?
Yes, ma'am.
Tell me something.
What's the difference between
an honest officer and a corrupt officer?
So, difference between the two, ma'am.
A corrupt officer--
A corrupt officer takes bribe,
and honest one doesn't. It's very simple.
Right, ma'am.
What will a corrupt officer
say to a passenger he pulls aside?
What will he say? He will say that…
- Will he ask for a bribe?
- Dhuria.
He won't say it to his face.
We are customs officers.
We have some dignity, don't we?
Right, ma'am.
He will tell the passenger
that you have been caught
for alleged evasion of a 100k custom duty.
Now, what do you want to do?
How do you want to do it? How much
do you want to give? That's hand in glove.
- Oh, so this is what it is.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- But forget this word here. Okay?
- Or I will PK you.
- PK, ma'am?
- I'll tell you some other day. Come on.
- Okay, ma'am.
- Would you like to have something?
- No.
No. Nobody… Nobody wants anything. Go, go.
Okay, ma'am.
Sir.
Go, get the checklist.
- Just come when I call you. Okay?
- Okay, bhai.
CHHATRAPATI SHIVAJI MAHARAJ
INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT
Arjun! Here are the couriers
for the flight that is about to land.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to Mumbai.
The local time is 20:25,
and the temperature is 27 degrees.
Please remain seated
with your seatbelts fastened,
until the seatbelts sign is turned off.
Be carefull when opening overhead bins.
As contents may have shifted
during the flight.
On behalf of Sitaara and the entire team,
thank you for flying with us.
We'd love to see you again soon.
Assalam-alaikum, Aslam bhai.
We got our baggage. Send for the car.
No, there was no problem at all.
- Yes, bhai. Okay, bhai.
- Get the car. Hurry.
- Patel, come in.
- Yes, Patel here.
Couriers have been identified.
Two women with a little girl, and two men.
Total five people in the group.
They just passed the green channel.
- Over and out.
- Roger that. Over and out.
Awasthi! Awasthi!
These people went straight
to parking in Departures.
Get the car to Departures. Hurry!
Sir, I'm stuck in traffic.
It'll take me ten minutes
to reach Departures.
Hey, move!
Stop the car! Stop!
- Sir, who are you?
- Follow that car! Follow that car!
- But who are you, sir?
- See the ID and move!
- Get moving!
- Yes, sir. I am.
Patel, come in.
Shit.
- Prakash sir, come in.
- Go, Arjun.
One flight is yet to take off.
We'll start the operation as soon it does.
And two domestic flights
are also about to land.
Can you delay them for ten minutes? Over.
- Let me talk to the ATC.
- Thank you, sir.
Subhash, we need to delay
two flights at the domestic airport.
- Stop, stop, stop! Pull over.
- Okay, sir.
Salaam.
Maria.
Sameer! Take the bags.
- Hey!
- Yes, sir?
Do you have a phone? Give it to me.
Here.
- What's the password?
- One-two-three-four.
Arjun.
Team leader to all.
Operation Longshot is on.
I repeat, Operation Longshot is on.
- Okay. Attention, everyone.
- Ma'am.
- Shree, you know your markings. okay?
- Okay.
Post one person at each spot.
- And don't make any mistake.
- Sure.
Dhuria, you know
what we have to do, right?
Sure, ma'am.
Sahib, if you are not using the phone.
Can I make a call?
Hey! Open the door!
- Hey! Who are you?
- Go, grab a bite, kiddo.
Who the hell are you?
I will tell you.
First, tell me who are you shadowing here?
Hey! I have my ID card in my front pocket.
See for yourself.
- Look. Hey! Let go!
- Scoot over!
What are you doing so far away
from the glitter and glam of the airport?
If you guys don't want
to spend the rest of your lives in jail,
better get lost.
Come on, get lost! Get lost!
Stop! Show your boarding pass, please.
- What happened?
- Boarding pass, please.
- But why?
- Boarding--
- Excuse me, Captain.
- Yes?
AIU.
Have you paid the tax
for your wrist watch?
Wrist watch? What wrist watch?
The watch that was in the box
that's in your bag.
And the watch is under your sleeve, sir.
Nice watch, by the way.
This is a personal one.
- Of course, sir?
- It's a gift from a friend.
I understand, sir. Please come.
- I can prove it.
- Yes, sir. Please come.
Officer, trust me.
You need to believe me on this.
Everybody please remain seated.
Please sit down.
Some officers are coming for a check.
Everybody sit down, please.
Ma'am, sir! Sir, please sit down.
- Please, maintain the decorum.
- Please sit down.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
Sir! Sir, please sit down.
Did anybody exit the plane?
No.
Boarding pass, please.
Get your bags. Come with me.
- Why? What's the matter, ma'am?
- Nothing. Come.
Madam, boarding pass?
- What happened, ma'am?
- Nothing.
Come with me.
Get your bags.
- Is anything wrong?
- Nothing, ma'am. Come.
Come on. Hurry up!
Everything is good.
Let's go.
I'm not stopping you. Why are you,
why are you pulling on this lock?
- What happened?
- What you want?
See, see. Be cool. Be cool.
No need to do these things.
What happened to you? What are you doing?
- What is this?
- Why you stop me?
- We are not stopping…
Why?
- We are just doing our duty, sir.
- Why you check me?
I know what's going on.
Surprise. I really missed you.
But I didn't miss you.
Dammit! I'll have to give it up.
Come. I'll get you some water.
I'll get you some water.
Yes, bhai. Here comes our courier.
- Run, bhai!
- Get him!
Where are you running off to?
How long will they make us sit here?
Take this into custody. This one.
You checked these ones?
Take a photo.
All the best. Fly safe.
Yes, Ramesh bhai.
He is awake now.
No, he was alone in the cab.
I'll hand it over.
Talk to him.
- Yes?
- Patel?
Why did you have to do this?
We were such good friends.
I was forced to do it.
We had orders from the seniors.
- Did I cause you any loss?
- Tell me the truth. What is the matter?
There is nothing, Ramesh bhai.
Everybody wants to show off
in front of the foreign delegates.
Just think about it.
Had I wanted to make a case,
I'd have detained them
at the airport itself.
I believe you. Stay put till morning.
- Nazima!
- Yes, bhai.
Take care of him.
Get him something to eat or drink.
Hands up!
Stay where you are!
Hey!
Sit down!
Drop the gun!
Sorry, sir. Santosh Tiwari, DRI.
Yes, Ramesh bhai.
Bloody hell! I doubted it from the start.
Anna's been going
from one police station to other.
Why? What happened?
There's a big mess going on.
I'll call you back.
Arjun sir had instructed us
for the sake of your safety.
Stop! Stop! Follow that car!
If you are not using the phone.
Can I make a call?
I hope his noble intentions
won't end up compromising the operation.
Subtitle translation by: Monika Saraf