Taxi!
- Madh island?
- Madh island. Okay, sir.
- Sir?
- Wasim! All okay?
All okay, sir.
Hand over the phone to madam.
I'm at my kid's school, sir.
For a parent-teacher meeting.
Who the hell was going to inform me?
Sorry, sir. I had informed madam.
Hit the gas.
Priya!
Arjun?
Why did you send Waseem away?
- Arjun, his kid--
- You should've called me.
He had a parent-teacher meeting
at his kid's school.
But what's the matter? Tell me.
I spared Priya today, Arjun.
Mend your ways.
Because if you don't listen to me,
then I will hunt her down.
She'll die a death much worse than Gujjar.
You can change the safe house,
but I'll track her down.
You can change again, I'll find her again.
All the safe houses in the world won't be
enough for you to hide her, Arjun Meena.
So don't forget
how valuable today's gift was.
What happened? Who was it?
Pack your stuff.
I will have to move you somewhere else.
Choudhary knows about this safe house.
Come on.
Wait a second, wait a second!
Priya, try and understand.
- Priya, please.
- Arjun!
I can't take this anymore.
Priya!
Send Arjun Meena in here.
The number you are trying
to call is currently not reachable.
Come in.
How are you?
I am good, sir.
The situation
has gotten out of hand, Arjun.
Mukim's custodial death,
Ramesh bhai being killed by this Dhuria,
and now Gujjar's murder.
I'm transferring your team
to the back office.
Lie low. Back track. And plan a strategy.
We have to get this bastard.
Yes, sir.
Arjun!
Sir.
There were three watches
listed as seized by Gujjar.
His informer's name is missing.
Do you know who it is?
I saw the report. There
were three luxury watches in your name.
You want to keep
your informer a secret, bastard?
No. No idea, sir.
Gujjar's informer is still there
in Choudhary Syndicate?
But nobody knows who it is.
They are worth 50 crores.
The informer
would've gotten a hefty reward.
- Okay.
- Sir.
Shrikant Saxena.
When Ravinder and I were close,
he used to share everything with me.
One day, I asked him…
Who do you trust the most in your batch?
Arjun. You've met him, right?
Yes.
Meenu?
In case something happens to me, remember…
What nonsense?
Hey, listen to me.
In case something happens to me,
you must share this name with Arjun.
Superintendent Shrikant Saxena.
He will know what to do.
Please?
Nothing's gonna happen to you.
Okay, my love. Nothing will happen.
But just in case…
Okay. Tell me what's the name I told you?
Superintendent Shrikant Saxena.
- Awasthi.
- Sir?
I need Superintendent Shrikant Saxena's
address. Right away.
Sharma ji, Arjun needs to be dealt with.
He's made life hell for us.
Sharma ji.
Oh, Arbab sahib!
- How are you?
- I'm fine.
Omar sahib was remembering you.
But we are headed to the hotel.
You can go later. Come on.
- Sharma ji, what is this?
- We'll have to go.
Omar sahib gave you
500 kilos of gold on my assurance.
You had promised three days.
It's been eight days.
Omar sahib wants to now
when will you pay him back?
Look, Omar sahib…
Omar sahib, what happened
was that the consignment…
Thank you.
Excuse me.
- Hello?
- I have bad news for you, Choudhary sahib.
I am going through Priya's file.
She only gave tips about gold and drugs,
as she knew about those.
She wasn't even aware of the watches.
There's somebody else in your Syndicate,
who is informing the Customs,
Choudhary sahib.
Find him or we will keep on taking hits.
I know who it is.
Tell me something.
I want to send two tons of goods
in two days. Will you be able to manage?
I will have to, as we are partners now.
It will be done. Don't you worry at all.
Okay.
My system takes care
of a lot of people and families.
And even I don't know
to what extent I can go to protect them.
I'll have to learn.
I'll have to learn this style,
Choudhary sahib.
And in this process of learning, why don't
I help expand and strengthen your system?
Want to talk business, Choudhary sahib?
Good, you showed me your true colors.
I had almost started trusting humanity.
Here's my offer.
Twenty percent of all profits.
After expenses.
As part of expenses,
sometimes your goods might be seized.
Don't mind that.
What will I get in return for this 20%?
You will get Mumbai International Airport,
including Customs.
Why didn't you say this earlier?
You seized so much of our stuff.
You could've said it upfront.
Valuation, Choudhary sahib.
I had to wait for the correct valuation.
Now that you know
how much pain I can cause you,
it'll be easier for you to evaluate
the true value of my worth.
What about this army of good guys
that you've brought to the airport?
I brought them in. I'll take them out too.
Hmm.
So you wish to ride the lion?
We only live once, Choudhary sahib.
What's the fun
if one didn't even ride the lion?
- Deal.
- Thanks.
Now that we are partners,
here's my first piece of information.
One of my teams is going to raid
Ramesh bhai's house at 10:30 a.m. sharp.
If Ramesh bhai survives, it's good for us.
And if he dies,
that too at the hands
of one of my Customs' team member,
that'll be more profitable for us.
We have a new recruit, Kulveer Dhuria.
He is greedy. He's broke.
Offer him a crore.
- Hello.
- Why did you do that to me?
Omar sahib,
I'll pay you back in full by next week.
But for that, you'll have
to give me two more tons.
What do you think?
Should we trust him again?
He is here, sir, talk to him.
Look, Omar sahib.
You know one has to spend money
to earn money.
As soon as
this consignment lands in India,
all your debt,
old and new will be paid off.
How will you send it?
And what's the guarantee
that it won't be seized this time?
Trust me, Omar sahib.
Nobody will dare touch this batch.
Sorry, Choudhary sahib.
Arbab hadn't mentioned that he'd take you
straight to Omar sahib from the airport.
It wasn't right on his part.
He's taken a big hit.
Had I been in his shoes,
I'd have done even worse.
Rahul, you got Priya
into the Syndicate, right?
Yes, Choudhary sahib.
I'm sorry for that.
No, no. Don't be.
You'll make up for it. Trust me.
Suresh.
There is only one way
out of this mire for us.
Sharma ji?
We have to send two tons of gold to India.
- In the next 48 hours.
- Two tons?
In one shipment?
Forty Indian tourists
have died in an accident.
Suresh, you are the only one
who can do this.
Doctors are on standby in Al Rasheed.
And if we wish--
No. Body concealment?
It will be very risky.
Caskets, I mean coffins will be perfect
for such a large consignment.
Superintendent Arjun Meena. Come in.
Take off your shoes.
Sure, sir.
My wife, Suman passed away three months
before I was released from prison.
I'm sorry, sir.
And I'm sorry for Gujjar.
I had told him to stay level-headed.
But no.
Youngsters, these days
hardly listen to the elders.
Twelve years ago, when I was terminated
based on a false accusation of corruption,
I had a source in the Al Dera Syndicate.
And he is still active today.
He sent me intel about the watches.
And I passed it on to Gujjar.
Gujjar had told me that if anything
happened to him, I should tell you this.
There were three watches
listed as seized by Gujjar.
The informer's name is missing.
Do you know who it is?
Timing.
Yes, Zubair. Tell me.
Sahib, two tons of Choudhary's gold
will land in Mumbai
day after tomorrow
in coffins carrying corpses.
- Two tons?
- Yes.
Hey, hello! Please stop.
- Who, sir? Me?
- Yes. Please stop.
- What is it, sir?
- Nothing. What is your name?
Suresh Tande.
- Where are you coming from?
- From Al Dera, sir.
I've scanned my baggage and everything.
Amazing.
You are well versed with our procedure.
Come, I need to do some checking.
Please come.
Come on. Please, please.
Please.
You can see, sir. All household stuff.
Look, my kid loves cars, sahib.
He races them.
This chocolate is also for my kid, sahib.
And dates, my family loves these, sahib.
So I brought these for them.
A friend of yours told me
that you're carrying stuff.
He will get rewarded too.
Sahib, there… are more dates.
These are of a better quality.
So I got these too.
Those guys do this because…
while I am busy with your paperwork,
their couriers can pass
through with their stuff.
Do you get it?
How much are you carrying on your body?
Sahib.
Sahib, my wife is really sick, sahib.
It's the last stage, sir.
I am here to see her, sahib.
So sad.
Hey, but how much are you carrying?
I have two kilos, sir.
Look, sir. I will…
surrender all the gold here.
Let me go and see my wife, sahib.
It is more than 50 lakhs.
You will have to be taken to court.
Sahib, please do something.
The courts closed for two days, so you--
- No, sahib. Don't do that.
- You will have to stay here.
- Don't do that, sahib.
- Hey, the courts are off, so…
- You have to stay here for two days.
- Sahib.
I have to see my wife. Please let me go.
I'll keep you in my prayers forever.
Let me go, sahib.
I am willing to do anything, sahib.
Let me go, sahib. Please, sahib.
- Tell me what can you do for me?
- I will do anything, sahib.
I'll do whatever you say.
So tell me…
who gave you the two kilos of gold?
He goes by the name
of Anna Seth, sahib. Anna Seth.
He is a labor contractor, sahib.
He has an office at Dera.
In Al Dera.
Where does this Anna get the gold from?
That I do not know, sahib.
I swear, I do not know. Trust me, sahib.
How long have you known Anna?
He came to Mumbai three years ago, sahib.
He was looking for workers.
And I got hired. I'm a welder, sahib.
When did you start this work?
One year ago, sahib.
I was in dire need of money, sahib.
I was trying to save my wife
at any cost, sahib.
So I was forced to do this, sahib.
Sahib, please let me go, sahib.
Let me go, sahib.
Okay, you can go today.
Thank you so much.
But from today onwards,
you will work for me.
I don't get it, sahib.
I mean that from today onwards,
you will work for me
and I'll tell you how to cozy up to Anna.
You will also get rewarded
for the gold you help us seize. Got it?
Okay. I will do that, sahib.
I will do anything.
Okay. Put your clothes on and get going.
Thank you, sahib.
- Two tons?
- Yes, sahib.
Omar sahib is pressurizing him to pay
him back. That's why he is doing this.
I was the one who gave him the idea.
You can forward this intel.
And sahib, if this consignment is seized,
it'll be the end of Choudhary Syndicate.
Okay, sahib, I will leave for Al Dera Mall
after dispatching the consignment.
Now, you have to help me get out of here.
I will try, Zubair.
You are aware that…
Yes, sahib. Your officer,
Ravinder Gujjar got killed.
I get it, sahib.
But don't worry. I will manage somehow.
No, no, no, no! Not you, I will manage.
Okay, sahib, one more thing.
I don't know if this is useful for you,
but Bada Choudhary is here.
And Bada Choudhary will stay here till
his contraband doesn't land in Mumbai.
Keep me posted after every six hours.
Okay, sir.
Forty coffins carrying two tons of gold
are going to land
at Mumbai International Airport
in the next 48 hours.
Put it on the table over there.
Kaka.
He's really betrayed us, Choudhary sahib.
- I will not spare him.
- You can settle that later, Anna.
It's time for our cargo.
Do what I've told you.
Okay, Choudhary sahib.
Yes, Saxena sahib.
My source has been compromised.
His life could be in danger.
Sir, please tell me what can I do?
I don't know.
Get him out of there at any cost.
Saxena sahib--
Don't waste time, Arjun!
And don't forget that Suresh
was working for your friend, Gujjar too.
And one more thing.
Choudhary is also in Al Dera now.
Thanks for taking my call
and picking me up.
Rahul!
Are you mad at me?
Hey! Why would you think I'm mad at you?
Choudhary sahib, I've picked her up.
We are coming straight to you.
Hey! What are you talking about?
Read the details at number two.
Aero details, Flight AEO-017.
Cargo details, 40 coffins. So?
But it doesn't state that each coffin
comes with 50 kilos of yellow.
How much?
- Fifty kilos.
Are you serious?
We will head for the cargo terminal soon.
Yes, sir.
Get the car.
I've to go to the cargo terminal.
Who's the clearing agent here?
It's me, sir.
Put this in the scanner.
Sahib, their families
have been waiting since 10:30 am.
If I tell them that we're
scanning their deceased relatives,
- sahib, it will lead to chaos.
- Let it be.
Take these away.
- Come on, guys. Let's go.
- Come on.
Get all the boxes loaded.
I know who it is.
Two tons of gold has to reach India.
Coffins would be perfect
for such a huge consignment.
It's time for our cargo.
Our gold won't be sent in coffins,
but in furniture,
as diplomatic cargo on the other flight.
- Which cargo is this?
- Diplomatic cargo, sir.
- From where?
- From the Kingdom of Burundi.
- What's in there?
- It's the diplomat's personal furniture.
Yes?
Choudhary sahib, first of all,
thank you for sparing my life.
But you'll never
be able to achieve the goal
for which you spared my life.
Arjun will never befriend you.
That's bad news for you.
And the bad news for you is that
you don't even know the name of the person
who was being tipped off
by Suresh kaka all this time.
So long as that person is active,
people like Suresh
will keep popping up in your syndicate.
If you wish, I can get Suresh kaka
to disclose that man's identity.
And what makes you think
that we are not capable of doing that?
I'm sure, you must have tried
in the past few hours.
- Good afternoon, sir.
- Good afternoon.
Is somebody here
for this diplomatic cargo?
Yes, sir. Their agents are outside.
You can go. I'll check it.
If your source gets compromised
12 hours before dispatch,
would you still let the consignment go?
Well, Arjun?
If your source gets compromised
12 hours before dispatch,
would you still let the consignment go?
Forget 12,
if I find out even three hours before,
I'll cancel the flight.
There will be no gold in the coffins.
Yes, Mitali.
- Arjun.
- Yes, tell me.
No gold was found here. It's all clean.
- When did this flight land?
- Just two hours ago.
- And where is its cargo?
- In Warehouse number 2, sir.
Sir, it's diplomatic cargo,
and household furniture. Sir!
Suresh kaka! Tell me,
who did you pass the information to?
Kaka, just a little while longer.
Choudhary sahib has promised
that he will not kill you.
Promise?
Move. Go, go, go!
Give me the name.
Suresh, give me the name.
Say it!
I have checked it all.
Take it up.
I'll call you back.
Take it inside.
Arjun!
What're you doing?
I am checking, sir.
This cargo is clear.
If Customs has any suspicions,
we can check it.
Arjun, this is diplomatic cargo.
We cannot open it.
Sir, we have reasons to believe,
this cargo contains gold.
And we need to inspect it.
What's your problem?
We cannot check diplomatic cargo.
Don't you know that?
It will be checked, Mr. Prakash Kumar.
Excuse me? What did you say?
It will be checked.
Arjun!
Stop it!
Suresh, give me the name.
Freeze! Nobody moves! Don't move!
Drop your weapons! Drop your weapons!
On your knees!
Do not move! Surrender!
You cannot escape.
You have been surrounded from all sides!
There is no way to escape.
You have been surrounded!
I repeat, surrender!
We'll be tracking you all the time. Okay?
It's okay, Arjun. I'll be fine. Trust me.
Really?
Aren't you scared?
No.
I know you have my back.
- Take care.
- I will.
Yes, Arjun?
Govind.
Go in with full backup.
The place where Priya is going,
entire Choudhary Syndicate will be there.
Well armed. Okay?
Don't worry.
We'll be prepared.
Priya!
Go, go, go, go!
Don't move.
Our external agencies…
…shared the intelligence
they had gathered
about Choudhary Syndicate
with foreign agencies.
And as a result,
all of Choudhary's locations were raided.
And his business was shut down.
Don't move.
You messed it all up.
Listen, I can explain this. Okay?
You guys are immature.
What will you do, huh?
Mitali!
Subtitle translation by: Monika Saraf