It's okay. It's okay.
Whenever we talk
about investigative agencies,
agencies like RAW, IB, CBI come to mind.
Very few people are aware that Customs
also has an intelligence department.
Which is known as COIN,
Customs Overseas Intelligence Network.
I'll explain the work
of COIN officers with a demo.
This is one
of our IPL superstar cricketers.
He is an all-rounder in everything.
He was in Rome for vacation.
He did some shopping,
along with sightseeing.
By some shopping,
I mean it was worth 10-15 crores.
The reality is, if you shop in Italy,
you can claim a VAT refund at the airport
on your way back to your home country.
VAT is similar to the GST we have here.
VAT is 22% here.
And the one watch our cricketer
has purchased itself is worth 2 crores.
Yes, yes, sir.
We certainly value the client…
My pleasure.
Since our cricketer
did shopping worth 10-15 crores,
his total VAT refund
comes to 2.5 to 3 crores rupees.
Our cricketer really enjoys the fact
that not only has he saved crores in duty,
but he is also getting cashback
by taking a VAT refund in Italy.
This is where COIN,
that is Customs Intelligence Network,
enters the scenario.
I won't share too many details
or you guys will also become alert.
But you better know that COIN officers
keep an eye
on every big transaction abroad.
And they share this information
with the Indian Customs immediately.
Hey, buddy! I've just landed.
So where do you want to meet up?
And when our favorite cricketer
crosses the green channel
without paying any duty,
AIU is right there to welcome him.
Courtesy COIN officer.
Just a sec. How many bags do you have?
- Are these your check-in bags?
- Yes. Four bags.
- You did a lot of shopping.
- What?
- Do you have the papers for this?
- Excuse me.
It was with the help of my colleague,
COIN Officer Govind
that I helped Priya escape from Al Dera.
Just a sec. Excuse me.
Just a sec. Move please.
Yes. Okay?
Okay, Ramesh bhai.
Customs has nabbed
them all with the stuff.
- What are you saying?
- They even got Aslam and Mukim.
Dammit!
Rahul! Yes. Yes, okay.
Start the car. Hurry.
Mumbai Customs nabbed 1,200 crore
of smuggled goods today in one shift.
WHOLE TRUTH
BEHIND THE SMUGGLERS' ARREST
They caught 500 kilos of gold,
2500 micro GPU chips,
hundred kilos of cocaine
and many expensive watches.
With this huge seizure,
Mumbai Customs has set a new record.
The operation led
by Assistant Commissioner Prakash Kumar
was a huge success
and a big blow to the smuggling syndicate.
It was a team effort
and entire credit goes to my team.
I also want to thank my seniors
for giving us full support.
It wouldn't have been possible
without them.
If so much gold was seized in one day,
just imagine how much gold
must be entering India illegally.
Salaam alaikum, Omar sahib.
Yes, I was also watching that. I'll do it.
Help him. Help him.
Tie up!
Tie Up. Slowly, slowly.
Help him. Lift it up.
Slowly, slowly. Close the door.
Anna.
The chic conned us in collusion
with the Customs, Choudhary sahib.
Let's get a few of them killed,
they'll all come around.
Killing government officers
like this is not right.
It's only once in awhile
they do their duty.
Try explaining it to them one more time.
Okay, Choudhary sahib.
I want that girl, Anna.
I've put my men on her trail,
Choudhary sahib. Don't you worry.
Excuse me! Sir, sir!
- What are you doing?
- I'm cleaning the stains.
- This is not allowed, sir.
- Hey, don't waste your time on me.
There is a box of brass inside this,
which has my medicines.
That stupid in-line officer of yours
thought it to be a gold brick.
- Please come with me.
- Why?
I want to check your bag.
I won't let you do that. What'll you do?
- What did you say?
- I won't let you.
Sir, please come with me.
Who gave authority to people like you?
I'm not here to give you
the name of who did or didn't--
Two guys went with contraband
behind your back.
- And you are after me?
- Come with me, please.
- I'm not going.
- It's you, Saxena sahib!
- How are you, sir?
- How do you know me?
Sir, I'm Superintendent Arjun Meena.
I attended your lecture in Delhi.
- Yes.
- Your lecture was awesome, sir.
Explain it to this fool.
Sir, who was this man
who spoke to you like that?
Shrikant Saxena sahib was
the most honest officer in Mumbai Customs.
He is. He is the most honest officer.
- Sir, I was checking his bag--
- No problem. Go.
- Shall I go and apologize?
- No need. Go.
- Come in.
- Good morning, sir. You asked for me?
Thank you. Thank you, sir.
Call you later, sir.
Okay. Bye, sir.
Good morning, young man.
Well done. Just well done.
Good, you didn't inform me about the raid.
I would have gotten distracted
during the conference.
Sir, full credit goes to the team.
It was entirely their doing.
They informed me at the last minute.
- You were busy with the foreign delegates.
- Oh, no. You did the right thing.
I'd have done the same.
Okay, how's the investigation
coming through?
Sir, the drug smugglers
have been taken into judicial custody.
And gold smugglers
are being gently interrogated by my team.
Very good.
Now, go home fast and pack your bags.
- You have to leave for Bangkok urgently.
- Bangkok, sir?
Finance Secretary-level talks
are being held there.
Gupta was supposed to go, but he is sick.
You'll have to substitute for him.
- Sir, there's a lot of workload here.
- There's nothing much.
Don't worry. You have a great team. Right?
They'll manage. You're flying out tonight.
My PA will give you
the briefing note, okay?
- Priya, ready?
- Yeah.
CUSTOMS ACT
60 GLORIOUS YEARS
Sir.
Hey, stop! Stop, you bastard!
Hello. All well?
Yes, all is well.
We've reached the safe house.
Good.
Is…
Just a sec. I'll hand it over.
Priya, it's Arjun.
Hello!
You okay?
I'll see you tonight.
- Bye.
Mitali! Mitali! You'll kill him.
Come on, let's go.
Easy. Calm down.
Calm down.
- Cheers!
- Well done, guys.
- Thank you, sir.
Man of the match!
The hero of this raid.
- Patel sahib!
- Congratulations, sir.
- You killed it. Good.
- Hey, you crushed it.
What killed it? I was trying to be a hero
and ended up losing 50 lakh rupees.
Now I'll have to take a loan
to send my daughter to Canada.
Ever heard of a Customs Superintendent
taking a loan, have you?
That's how things work in this team,
Patel sahib.
So, let's toast to celebrate his loss…
- Cheers!
Bottoms up, sir.
- Okay. Cheers. Sit.
- Please sit.
Please sit, sir.
Sir, I had a question. I've heard there's
a cap on our reward money. Is that true?
Dhuria. Now you want a reward
just for doing your duty?
- No, sir. I was just asking--
- Hey, nothing wrong in asking.
Do you have any idea
how much today's informer is going to get?
- How much?
- Crores of rupees.
My boy, if you love money,
then in your next life,
forget about being a customs officer,
better be an informer.
- Sir… What…
- Yes, bhai.
Arjun!
Prakash sir didn't come?
He had to leave for Bangkok urgently.
Gujjar, come here for a sec.
- Have some manchurian.
- Okay.
- Go on, have some, ma'am.
- We got it for you.
Oh, that! Strain it and give me.
I saw the report.
You seized three luxury watches. Congrats.
So, you want to keep
your informant a secret, asshole?
You've kept yours a secret too.
- Cheers!
Okay, listen. Meet me
in the detention room tomorrow morning.
It's our turn to bat.
- Just call me.
- I think alcohol gives a good kick.
Okay, guys. Enjoy yourselves.
I have some work to do.
What work do you have
at this hour of the night?
It's girl trouble, guys. Girl trouble.
- Bye.
- Good night.
Bye, sir.
- Bhasin, all okay?
- All okay, sir.
Were you scared?
No.
I knew you had my back.
Vincent!
Thapa, pass the water.
Start talking. Or the thrashing continues.
Look, sahib. We are the middlemen.
We get the goods.
And deliver it to the concerned party.
Apart from that, we know nothing.
You can thrash us all you want.
Sahib, I want my lawyer.
No. Your lawyer
won't be here for two days.
Till then, we'll continue
with our hospitality.
Come on, get moving.
Arjun, if our beatings
leave any marks on their bodies,
it could be a problem in court.
Don't worry about that.
I have their medical certificates ready.
But we need to get them to talk.
Thapa? Here.
Record a video. Carry on, bhai.
- What are you doing, sahib?
- Recording a video. What else?
What's the video for?
So that all your neighbors
can see you getting thrashed.
This clip will be forwarded
to all your pals, your girlfriends,
your bhabhis in JJ Junction.
You guys will be famous.
Hey, listen. Take off his shorts.
No, sir. Hey, don't!
Sahib, if you want to make a video,
make a good one at least.
Get some proper lighting.
So our faces look decent.
Turn off the camera, sir.
- I will tell you everything.
- Hey, Mukim!
To hell with this, bhai.
My reputation in JJ Junction
won't be scarred
just to safeguard the Gujarati.
Turn off the camera, sir.
Thapa?
Hey! Get me some water.
Get some tea for me. Get my clothes.
Ramesh managed all of Choudhary's goods
that landed in Mumbai.
Where does Ramesh bhai live?
He lives somewhere in Madh island.
I have his number saved in my cell.
Under the name Boss number two.
- Who is Boss number one?
- My wife.
Unlock it.
- Vincent.
- Yes, sir.
Check who is there at DRI?
Go and get this Ramesh bhai.
Sure, sir.
Jai Hind, sir.
Jai Hind, Prakash. Reached safely?
Yes, sir.
- I was just leaving for the embassy.
- Good.
Somebody is waiting for you
outside your room. Go, meet him.
Who wants to meet me in Bangkok, sir?
That's the surprise. Hurry up, go.
Right, sir.
Yes, Arjun? What's the status?
Sir, we got Mukim's statement.
The Ramesh bhai he is talking about
has direct links to Bada Choudhary.
We are going to get Ramesh bhai.
That's good news. Keep me updated.
- How are you, Prakash ji?
- I'm good.
Please come.
Welcome to Bangkok, Prakash ji.
Ranjeet. Ranjeet Choudhary.
My photos published in papers
have my name as Bada Choudhary.
Hey, guys. I'm working on a play.
So, there's a Madrasi character,
Bala Nair in the play.
Will anybody help me prep for the role?
Yes, I can help you.
You have to learn the difference
between a Madrasi and a Malyali.
Hey, look! There's Meenakshi with a baldy.
Where?
Was that guy bald?
He's saying it was a baldy.
- Why are you laughing?
- Sir, sorry. Sir, he--
How long have you been in service?
Sir, I… I'm sorry, sir.
Rascal, you're on probation
and laughing at a senior?
No, sir. No, sir.
- Sorry, sir.
- How dare you?
- Sir, sorry, sir.
- Do you wanna stay in the job or not?
Yes, yes. Sorry, sir.
This is what you call acting.
- What's this school bag you carry around?
- This… is just like…
- Hey.
- What are you doing?
Bhai.
Bhai, why are you stressing?
My words carry no value.
I'll change my statement
before the magistrate.
Here. Your wife's calling. Talk to her.
Hello. Salaam alaikum, Rubina.
Yes. All well?
Don't worry.
I'll get bail in two days.
Yes.
Take care. Allah hafiz.
Bhai, is bhabhi upset?
Bhai. Don't be mad, bhai.
Bhai, I forgot to tell you.
You know, Reshma from Temkar Street?
She's started working in the godown line.
Tell me, bhai. Does it look good?
Complete all the formalities and draft
a request to the Ministry of Finance.
Okay, sir.
Hello?
Why did you do this to me?
Just a sec.
Look, Prakash. I just arranged
the meeting so that you could go there--
Sir, I held you in high regard.
Prakash, you're still young. You don't
understand the limitations of our job.
What did Choudhary say?
First of all, I apologize
for calling you to Bangkok like this.
Yes. There was no conference.
I wanted to meet you.
Why did you want to meet me?
I want to be friends with you, Prakash ji.
Enmity is a tremendous waste
of time and effort.
I believe in the saying that money
can buy everything in this world.
Those who say, it can't,
don't know how to shop well.
And I consider myself
very good at shopping.
My syndicate takes care of your boss,
a lot of the officers
and staff at your airport.
We run so many households.
Daughters' marriages, kids' education,
hospital bills of many are taken care of.
It's a very well-oiled system.
It's smooth. And at its peak performance.
And then, an officer like you steps in.
And he brings along
a few more honest officers,
who become a threat to our system.
And I don't like threats, Prakash ji.
That's why I want to be friends with you.
The system takes care
of a lot of people, a lot of families.
And even I don't know
how far I'd go to protect them.
Do you know what country means, Choudhary?
It is much bigger
and greater than your system.
You need 10-20 corrupt officers
to run your system, right?
But just one honest person
is enough to run my country.
Prakash ji, if I wish I can get you posted
at some prestigious foreign embassy.
You can earn dollars and live in luxury.
Or I can send you to Nathu La,
where you'd be dealing with cheap products
from China in the biting cold.
But what's the need for that?
We have nothing personal
against each other.
Then why are you
after my bread and butter?
Because your business
is destroying my country.
Breaking news. Your country
is already a wreck, Prakash ji.
You better watch the news.
Write down any amount you want.
You and your team will get it every month.
And you will also get a regular tip.
So that your team's reputation
stays intact.
This is our last meeting, Prakash ji.
No. We will meet once more, Choudhary.
Sir, you sent me to meet
a criminal under false pretenses.
He's telling me
that he is running our department.
Nobody is running anything here, Prakash.
We all do what we can, for our survival.
I suggest you not get too excited.
- Open the gate.
- Sahib is not at home.
You…
- Come on, move.
- Come on.
- Open the gate.
- Move.
Come on.
Vincent.
Wait! You can go.
- What is it?
- We are here for Ramesh bhai.
He has gone on a pilgrimage.
He'll be back in a month.
You can come then.
We want to search the place.
- Boys.
- Yes, sir.
Hey, young man! Take off your shoes.
This is our temple.
Wait.
There's nothing in here. Move on.
Let's check outside.
He killed my son! He killed my son!
Sir, I didn't do anything.
Sir, I swear, I didn't do anything.
Sir, he had the gun in his hand. The gun
went off by itself during the scuffle.
Sir, believe me. Sir, I swear. I did not
do anything. I did not do anything.
Sir, he shot himself.
Sir, please believe me, sir.
I swear, I did not do anything…
Mukim.
Mukim!
These bastards killed my Mukim, sir!
They killed him! Mukim!
He killed Mukim!
He is the one who killed him, sir!
Mukim!
They killed my Mukim, sahib.
Subtitle translation by: Monika Saraf