Hey! Stop!
Where are you running off to? You mother…
Leave me! Leave me, woman!
Hey! Stop!
Stop!
I will kill you if you don't move.
Move ! Move it!
Move! Let's go. Let's go.
Water?
Madam, have some water.
Hey, you ran so much.
Why don't you want water, Swati?
Your system will get upset. Come on.
Is your belly full?
Arjun Meena, so this is all your doing?
Hey, let go of my hand. Hey. Let go!
Ramesh bhai, if you want the girl,
you have to pay 50 lakhs.
Send someone to the helipad.
I'll be there in an hour.
Hold on a little longer.
Then you can relax all you want.
My name is Arjun Meena.
I work as a Superintendent in Customs.
But I'm under suspension right now.
There's a long story behind my suspension.
I'll tell you about it some other time.
For now, let's start from the beginning.
Spread over 2,000 acres,
Mumbai International Airport
is one of the busiest airports
of the world.
This airport which handles
over 1,000 flights
and over 150,000 passengers daily,
also gets 30,000 tons of cargo every year.
For centuries, the places at the center of
travel and business also faced taskaree.
Taskaree… which means smuggling.
If you buy any item
over 50,000 from a foreign country,
you have to pay a duty on that item.
How many pay this duty?
Let's not dwell on it.
But the simple definition of taskaree is
bringing anything illegally
into the country.
Anything from gold to betel nut.
These taskars, meaning smugglers,
smuggle everything
that fetches them profit.
But before pocketing the profit,
these smugglers have to browbeat us.
Who are we? We are the worst nightmare
for the smugglers of the world.
Seema Shulk Adhikari,
meaning Customs Officer.
For thousands of years, smugglers
and we have been playing hide and seek.
Sometimes, they win. Sometimes us.
Sometimes it's a win-win.
Just like every day,
some smugglers have left for Mumbai
from across the world.
Let's see who wins today.
There's a total of 50 bags.
Declare these three iPhones.
The pickup will meet you at Arrivals.
Hand these over to him.
- Hello, sir. Mikki speaking.
- Yes, Mikki.
A one crore consignment
will land in your shift.
Settle for any amount you want,
but I'll take 1.5 lakh.
Agreed. Tell me the details.
They are bringing watches on TG 317.
- Who's bringing them?
- Hema Kangani. Seat number 14 A.
Okay.
- Any scope of one K?
- A lot more.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Seat 8 BEF.
Yeah, yeah. There it is.
Beta, left. On your left.
- Yeah. Here.
- This one, beta. This one.
You want to sit here?
Let's exchange. You come here. Okay?
- Thank you.
- It's okay.
Oh, nice. You got a window seat.
Thank you.
- Would you like to sit here?
- No. It's okay.
These four people are in the air
and they don't even know
what happened in Delhi 48 hours ago.
Two days ago, the opposition in Parliament
put the blame directly
on the Finance Minister for the loss of
40,000 crores annually
to our country due to smuggling.
And then what…
Enough Avinash.
I don't think I can take anymore.
With all due respect, sir,
we caught 722 kilos of gold
in the last financial year.
Every year, 300 tons of gold is coming
into our country through the airports.
And you caught only 722 kilos?
As Chairman, Customs,
is this not your failure?
Sir, please compare our customs
intelligence budget with other countries.
It's 100 crore.
Sir, what can be done in 100 crore?
Yes, we do have a reward system
like other countries. But how much?
Sir, a customs officer
cannot claim a reward
of more than 20 lakhs
in their entire career.
Many times, that too takes five years
to be disbursed. There's so much red tape.
Please think, for a person running
a 60,000 crore smuggling racket,
it's not a big deal to disburse
200 crore rupees to our officers.
So you are saying,
your officers are corrupt?
If that's the case,
what is your vigilance department doing?
How many officers were caught
red-handed and action taken against them?
Sir, corruption is present not only
among low ranks. Everyone is involved.
- Now, our system is such--
- Avinash!
I want a crack-down on this.
The media is knocking at our doors.
And elections are coming.
Prepare a list.
It should have some honest,
motivated and hungry officers.
These are rare species.
What did you say?
Sir, the officers who are honest,
motivated and hungry
are rare species.
In fact, they are
on the brink of extinction.
I'll need time to find them.
Forty-eight hours, Avinash.
That's all you have.
Sir.
Prepare a list of top officers. Right now.
A very intelligent man had said that
India has elections on a regular basis,
that's why it somewhat keeps progressing.
When you get orders from Delhi,
the government employees
redefine efficiency.
A list was made.
And throughout the country…
…young, hungry and motivated officers…
…got posted on strategic
and important airports overnight.
And Assistant Commissioner Prakash Kumar
was posted
at the Mumbai International Airport.
And from that day,
nothing remained the same.
She has arrived.
- Hi.
- Shalini ji.
What are you declaring today?
Just these three iPhones.
Okay.
- These are new models, right?
- Yes.
Your commission will reach
your home by evening.
Deposit 120,000 there and get
an acknowledgement on this receipt.
And get that bag scanned.
Okay. Your passport.
Have a good day.
Yes. Excuse me.
Madam, please stop.
- What is it, sir?
- You may go.
- You guys--
- It's nothing.
- Bye.
Madam, please come with me.
Yeah, please.
Madam, you've got
three watches in the bag?
Yes, they are for my grandchildren.
I mean, they are gifts. The cheap ones.
Can you show them, please?
Raju, put the bag on the table.
Receipt.
Nothing else?
You may go.
It is said that if these smugglers
put their mind to good use,
they can solve world hunger.
But they can't put their mind to good use.
Namaste, madam.
Please come.
- Hi!
- Hi.
- Yes, Bangkok was very interesting.
- Hey! What are you watching?
Thank you, madam.
- Thank you.
Sir.
- Sir.
- A.C. Prakash Kumar.
- Please have a seat.
- That's okay.
What is it? Why did you pull over?
The engine is making some noise.
Inside, inside. Inside.
Move.
Shut up!
Keep quiet!
Tell me.
We have your courier, Swati Salunkhe.
Our demand is 50 lakhs in US dollars.
Twenty-five lakhs.
Final offer. Share the location.
We'll inform you in one hour.
Raghu!
I have a job for you.
A.C. Prakash Kumar
reporting for duty, sir.
Your joining date is tomorrow, right?
Sir, I reached Mumbai last night.
I thought to check the airport
instead of wasting time.
A person like you is called
enthu cutlet in local slang.
Walk with me.
Sir!
Sir, I made a detailed report
on how to curb smuggling in this airport.
Firstly, we have to randomly change
the officers sitting in accounts shift.
This will ensure a--
- Put it in the car.
- Sir.
This will--
You think that my officers
are in collusion with the smugglers.
I don't know, sir.
You want to say that my officers
are corrupt, incompetent?
- Excuse me.
- Yes, sir?
Where are you coming from?
From Al Dera, sir.
- Any problem, sir?
- No problem. Just routine.
Let's check your bag.
Sir, it's a medical emergency.
I've to reach Pune.
My father is very critical.
- It'll take two minutes. Come.
- I'm already late. Sir, please.
Put your bag in there.
- Sir.
- Laptop bag.
- Sir, there's nothing in it, just laptop.
- I know it's a laptop. Put it.
Forward.
Pull back a little.
- Open it.
- Sir, sir.
Sir. Sir, sir.
It has very important data, sir.
It can crash.
Your data will be safe.
Sir, please stop.
I'll come with backup tomorrow.
- Then you can--
- Relax.
Sir, please, try to understand.
Just two minutes, my dear.
The screen will break. Please flip it.
Don't make a mess and keep quiet.
Sir, this is not mine. I swear by my mom.
Sir, the lady sitting besides me
had a brown bag. I think it got exchanged.
Sir, I…
Sir, I didn't do this. My dad's sick…
It was a good stunt.
Thank you, sir.
Sir, if you permit me
to post 30 new officers here,
I can raise a new team here.
Prakash, I know that you were
handpicked by the Finance Minister.
But you need to know
that I cannot transfer 30 officers
without a reason.
Hello, sir.
No problem, sir. Sure, sir, sure.
Welcome, sir. Welcome.
So, here comes
your first official assignment.
Mr. Siddharth Gupta is coming
on the Singapore flight today.
Take care of his protocol.
Taking care of the protocol means
making a VIP feel like a VVIP.
Please come, sir.
Prakash sir was given the task
of taking care of the protocol
for Siddharth Gupta,
the only son-in-law of a politician.
- Excuse me.
- Yes, sir?
- May I get one more?
- Sure, sir.
Prakash sir was not only young
and dedicated, but intelligent too.
He very well knew the result
of not giving the son-in-law
a proper welcome.
Prakash sir gave the son-in-law
such a welcome
that the son-in-law and officers
at Mumbai airport
will remember that welcome for years.
Excuse me. May I? Thank you.
Good afternoon, sir.
Nobody came to receive me at the airport.
Did you not inform anybody?
Sir, I talked to the commissioner myself.
- Give me two minutes, sir.
- Bloody hell!
Excuse me?
Why not just stroll in the garden?
Excuse me.
Zoom in Cam 14 on the hand.
- Thapa?
- Jai Hind, sir.
Jai Hind. How are you?
- Are you fine?
- Absolutely fine, sir.
When did you join here?
Did you take charge today?
What to say, Thapa?
You have got your network here also.
Yes, sir.
Thapa, tell me something.
Pawar sir.
Pawar sir is the best man for this.
Just a while back
a punter made a fool of Pawar sir.
Pawar sir is in a bad mood.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
- On the line…
- As it starts, the traffic is stuck.
Excuse me. AIU.
What is it?
You came through green channel.
Is there nothing to declare?
- What's your name, Officer?
- Aabhas Pawar.
Why do you want to know?
My name is Siddharth Gupta.
And I have nothing to declare.
So you are wearing a fake Piaget?
I bought it in Mumbai.
And I was wearing it when I left.
Who sold it to you in Mumbai?
Smart. Very smart.
Do one thing, Pawar.
Send someone with me outside.
I'll give you two lakh rupees.
For your snacks. Happy?
Come with me.
Pawar, I said it is not needed.
- Send someone out--
- Come with me.
- Pawar. Don't touch me. Where to?
- Where are you taking me? Leave my bag.
- Yeah.
- Don't touch me. Okay?
- Come on.
Where are you taking me?
Come with me inside. Come on.
- Come on.
- Let me see where you're taking me.
- Don't touch me. I'm telling you.
- Come.
- Where to? Tell me. Left, right? Where?
- Right.
Come in, sir.
You're giving me snack-money after saving
1.5 crore duty on a five crore watch?
You think, I'm a beggar?
- Listen.
- Take off your clothes.
Take off your clothes for strip search.
Come on.
Remember, there is no CCTV here.
I will give you a good thrashing.
Take off the clothes, mother--
Take them off.
Who are you calling?
Pawar, have you gone nuts?
Sir…
I didn't know
that he's Mr. Bhonsle's son-in-law.
Sir, why are we all being punished
for his fault?
- Why are we being transferred?
- Because you all were there with him.
It's the style of the powerful.
Now, no customs officer
will stop his son-in-law for ten years.
Sir, please do something.
My wife can't bear
the cold weather of Nathu La.
Sorry, my hands are tied.
I got a call from the Ministry.
Complete all your exit formalities
before the end of the shift.
Sir, please.
I told you to lead the protocol, Prakash.
I gave you a simple task.
I had to leave my granddaughter's party.
As my joining date was tomorrow,
so the system
did not generate
my I-Card and all access key-card.
You were in a hurry this morning,
so I didn't even get your number.
I didn't know anybody here.
So I was quite helpless.
By the time I got your number,
it was all over, sir.
This Pawar is an idiot.
Why did he have to do that?
- We are already short-staffed--
- Sir, this is a list.
Please revoke the suspension
of three officers.
These three will make a team themselves.
Arjun Meena,
Ravinder Gujjar, Mitali Kamat.
- Right, sir.
- Do you know them?
I don't know them personally,
but I do know about them.
- Yes, sir?
- Send Sawant inside.
What's up?
You wanna eat banana?
Go!
Let's go!
Moving out!
Let's move, let's move.
Raghu!
- Swati, are you okay?
- I won't spare that bastard.
He ran that way.
Swati, what are you doing?
Don't run or you'll be in trouble.
Hey!
Hey! Stop!
Where are you running off to? You mother…
Leave me! Leave me, woman!
Bloody…
Stop!
I will kill you if you don't move.
Move it! Move it!
Start the engine.
Move, move. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go.
The drugs that Swati Salunkhe
was bringing from Ethiopia,
I got a tip off about that
from an intelligence officer there.
And I forwarded the same tip off
to Moosa and Tony.
Water?
Madam, have some water.
You ran so much.
Why don't you want some water, Swati?
Your system will get upset. Come on.
Hey! Let go of my hand!
Ramesh bhai, if you want the girl,
you have to pay 50 lakhs.
Send someone to the helipad.
I'll be there in an hour.
Yes, Sawant sir. What is it?
Superintendent Meena,
your suspension has been revoked.
The new AC sir
wants to see you immediately.
I'm on my way.
Tell your boss
that my suspension has been revoked.
None of his couriers
will cross my airport from tomorrow.
Got it?
If you are now being so honest,
then return this money too.
Why are you collecting this ransom?
Because luck does not favor you.
I got the call to join the duty
after getting the money.
Had it come a little earlier,
your boss could have saved the money.
I got my job back,
but at that time
I had no clue of what lay ahead.
Subtitle translation by: Sanjay Malhotra