- Mom, I want a balloon.
- No, no.
- Please, Mom.
- It's Navya's birthday in two days,
we'll get it then. Okay?
- Okay. Promise?
- Yes, promise.
Tomatoes for sale!
- Hey, stop.
- Take some, madam. The tomatoes are good.
- How much?
- Seventy rupees a kilo, madam.
- What?
- Seventy rupees a kilo.
Are they made of gold?
- Madam, take some.
- Not at all.
- I'll give you a discount. Madam!
- No, leave it.
How much for the tomatoes?
- Fifty rupees a kilo, madam.
- And onions and potatoes?
Onion is 60 rupees a kilo
and potato is 55 rupees a kilo.
Don't fleece me by calling me madam.
Tell a fair price.
Madam, I'm giving you the best price.
- Why would I fleece you?
- Okay.
A kilo of onions, two kilo potatoes
and a kilo of tomatoes.
- Okay, please pick the tomatoes.
- Yes.
Baby, see? Red tomatoes. Only red. Okay?
Come on, put the red ones in this.
- Here you go.
- Your payment.
This is not four kilos.
No way, madam?
I just weighed it in front of you.
Give it to me. I will weigh it again.
See for yourself.
Listen, I can tell you that it's not
more than 3.5 kilos as I held the bags.
Either you tell me the truth
or face the consequences.
Shall I weigh it elsewhere?
I tipped the scale by ten percent.
It was my mistake. I'm sorry.
Replace the scales right now
and weigh it properly.
Okay.
- Good evening, sir.
- Good evening, Kamath.
The new AC has revoked your suspension.
Come to the office immediately.
Sir.
This is my department's
human weighing scale, Mitali Kamath.
Harder. Come on.
She's also known
as the Google of our department.
Customs officers are clueless
about the value
of a lot of things in the world.
But Mitali keeps track of the existence
of such exotic things and their value.
This is her gift, and her passion too.
She's a divorcee.
And she dotes on her daughter.
Kulveer Dhuria.
Where from? Chhattisgarh?
How long have you been working here?
- Who are you, man, huh?
- Santa Claus.
I've brought a gift for you,
just like Santa Claus.
Don't waste your time
on those hippie foreigners.
Let them go, you won't find a thing.
They are backpackers.
This couple is also not hiding anything.
They are bringing
some dead relative's ashes.
Look straight ahead.
Go and check that guy in the blue jacket.
He surely has something to declare.
But why are you telling me all this?
Because your face shows
that you haven't caught anyone to date.
Excuse me, sir. Hi.
Where are you coming from?
- Bangkok.
- Bangkok?
- Your passport, please.
- Sure.
Thank you.
Hey! What the hell is that?
- Sir, these are marmosets.
- What?
- Marmosets.
- Where did you get them from?
- Got them from Thailand, but--
- From Thailand?
Do you know they are illegal here?
Turn off your cameras, guys.
Turn off your cameras.
- Do you have permission for these?
- No, sir.
Then how could you bring them in?
Sir, they're pets for kids…
Kids liked them,
so you brought them along?
Didn't you check our rules?
These are pygmy marmoset monkeys.
It's illegal
to bring them into our country.
But they are a trend among the rich kids.
This guy bought
two of these small monkeys at Bangkok,
sedated them and put them in his
jacket pocket and brought them to India.
The flight was delayed by a few hours,
and the monkeys' sedation wore off.
And as soon as they came to their senses,
these little ones
started behaving like monkeys.
How did Santa Claus get to know that this
guy was carrying monkeys in his pocket?
God only knows.
This guy calls himself Santa Claus,
actually his real name is Ravinder Gujjar.
Gujjar is my best friend and batchmate.
Grandpa!
Gujjar's father, two of his brothers,
his sister and mother,
his paternal uncle and his wife,
his dad's sister and her husband
are employed in the Central Excise
or Income Tax department.
If there was a competition
for the most corrupt family in India,
Ravinder Gujjar's family
would've always won.
Come on, food is served. Come on.
Gujjar sort of hated this system
as he had grown up hearing their tales
of corruption since childhood.
So, on the first day he joined Customs,
he had vowed
not to accept bribe, not even a penny.
He hasn't broken that vow to date.
He is hardly respected in the family.
And everybody considers him to be crazy.
But Gujjar is not at all crazy.
He is a soft-hearted romantic guy.
Gujjar's love story is unique too.
He had been working for just 15 days
and he fell in love with the nice,
homely-looking Meenakshi,
who worked at the duty-free shop.
And Meenakshi liked Gujjar a lot too.
They got into a routine
and two years passed by.
Gujjar got into AIU.
Gujjar and Meenakshi
took breaks at the same time,
and had tea from the runway canteen.
At that time, Meenakshi wasn't aware
that Gujjar used
to take her for tea outside
because tea
was very expensive at the airport.
Meenakshi's parents also loved Gujjar.
As he made no mention of dowry
and said that he'd do a court marriage.
Everything is finalized.
You guys just have to sign.
I'll submit this, dates will be announced.
Then you'll get married in a jiffy.
Thank you. Done. I'll be back.
It happened just last month.
We were waiting for Meenakshi
and her family at the court…
…but she did not come.
Don't worry. No one died.
It so happened
that the day Meenakshi realized
that Gujjar was not trying to impress her
with his honesty.
He actually just wanted
to survive on his salary alone.
That day marked
the end of Gujjar's love story.
Ravinder, your exile is over.
Had I known that you were coming back too,
I'd have done a couple of more gigs.
Good one.
Your sense of humor is still intact. Good.
Fifty lakhs in here.
I found it under the washroom shelf.
Put it in the seizure.
Everything about you
looks very dicey to me.
Is it just me
or have you called others too?
Mitali and Ravinder.
How will it happen without the trinity?
Hey, Meena! Your suspension's over?
I don't know, man. Let's see.
Excuse me. Sir is ready for you.
Let me have a chat with him
and then we can…
Sir.
Right. Carry on. Call me in the evening.
- Hello.
- Arjun Meena reporting for duty, sir.
I've heard a lot about you.
- The most amazing things of course.
- Thank you, sir.
By the way, we've also been told
that a very young and dynamic officer
has joined the department.
This is Mitali Kamath and Ravinder Gujjar.
- Hello, sir.
- Hello, Mitali.
- Hi.
- Hi, sir.
My name is Prakash Kumar.
And I've been given the mandate
to end smuggling at this airport.
But I cannot do that without you three.
When I was chosen for this job,
I asked around
and got to know about you three.
And I was also told
the reason you guys were suspended.
But welcome back.
So long as I am here,
you needn't worry about anything.
Catch whoever you want.
But we've to ensure that smugglers forget
the Mumbai International Airport route.
Do your duty without any tension.
As long as you all
are playing by the book,
I will be responsible
for anything that happens to you.
- Understood?
- Sir.
- Yes, sir.
Our mission is
to destroy the Choudhary Syndicate,
which brings
the maximum contraband to Mumbai.
Based on intelligence from various sources
I have compiled a report
on the main players
of Choudhary Syndicate.
I want you all to have a look at it.
Choudhary Syndicate operates from London,
Italy, Middle East, Ethiopia and Bangkok.
The leader of
this entire Syndicate is Bada Choudhary,
who uses his brain to run
this entire syndicate
from Milan through his couriers.
Choudhary's back story
is quite interesting too.
It's a story of twin brothers.
Bada Choudhary and Chota Choudhary.
Just as Vijay worked as a laborer
in Deewaar so Ravi could go to school.
Similarly, Chota Choudhary ran
an illicit trade so as to educate Bada.
Betrayal?
Bada Choudhary worked hard in the hope
that he'd study hard
and make the younger one quit his ways.
But here, Chota's clout was growing.
And big gangs
were reaching out to hook up with him.
But he loved his freedom.
Join us.
And he didn't want to give it up.
NO
But the story took a turn the day
- Yes.
- Bada Choudhary became an engineer.
Pick it up. Hello?
He's become an engineer.
My brother is an engineer.
Chota Choudhary was very happy.
And he was on his way home when…
That day Bada burnt all his degrees
in his brother's pyre.
And he decided what
he wanted to do with his life.
With Sharma ji's help, he first
killed all those who had murdered Chota.
And then, on Sharma ji's advice,
he smuggled his first consignment.
Back in 2003,
mobile phones
were rapidly gaining ground in India.
Thousands were smuggling mobile phones.
But Bada Choudhary came up
with an idea to smuggle something unique.
Memory cards.
Smaller than two-inches,
thousands of memory cards
could easily fit into a small box.
Choudhary made 1.5 lakhs
with his very first consignment.
Choudhary had found his niche.
And that was smuggling.
And he started bringing everything
from abroad that had a margin to Mumbai.
As he was passing
through airports regularly, he understood
that some customs officers
could be bribed.
So he made deals with all of them.
An organized payment structure was set up.
And he began running his shady business
with complete integrity.
His business kept growing,
and he needed more people.
This is Anna,
his nephew Rahul, and this is Suresh.
They smuggle gold
from the Middle East into India.
Meetings with Anna
helped him understand the gold business.
Anna became his top officer in Al Dirah.
And this is Carlos Junior.
He sends drugs
from Ethiopia into our country.
The responsibility
of collection and sale of stuff
brought by the couriers
rests with Ramesh bhai.
This is Mrs. Syed, who handles
the operations in London and Italy.
She sends high-end bags
and luxury goods to India from there.
Been in business for 20 years,
Bada Choudhary's Syndicate
is India's biggest smuggling syndicate.
At a photo shoot
for a fashion show in Milan,
Choudhary's eyes fell on a swimwear model.
He fell for her and that model converted.
Bianca became a true Indian
and she got a new name, Binita Choudhary.
They have a four-year-old son now.
And the happy family
lives comfortably in a villa on Lake Como.
Now, what I am going to tell you
stays inside this room.
The three of you will work
for Central Intelligence Unit from today.
Arjun, you will lead this op.
To the outside world,
you are still the same.
You'll continue to do what you were doing.
There is no other way
to flush out corruption from the system.
From today, our only goal will be
to eliminate the Choudhary Syndicate.
Find smugglers, find corrupt officers
and let's do a thorough clean up.
- Clear?
- Right, sir.
Sir, we will need more people.
Send me a list.
Sir, may I ask a question?
Hope you won't be transferred soon?
No, I mean you brought us here and then--
I'm here till the election results.
I don't know after that.
Good to know, sir.
You just don't think, do you?
You just say what you want.
Hey, what did I say? We need to know.
He has put us on the hook,
hope he will stick with us.
- It's simple, man.
- Just a sec.
Hello.
Don't create a scene here. I can explain.
No, there's no need for that.
I just came to give you this.
That'll be 450 rupees.
Two hundred for the sweets
and 250 for the garland.
You've come to ask me for money?
Yes, why? That was my hard-earned money.
I was going to spend it on our wedding.
You don't want to marry me,
return my money.
Hand it over.
Neha, give me 500 bucks.
Give me 500 bucks.
- What happened?
- Just give me.
- Oh, man.
- Keep the change.
Hey, madam. I'm not a waiter
that I'll keep the change.
I am a Customs Officer. Do you get it?
"Keep the change."
Meena, come here.
Hey, come here, bro.
Give her 50 bucks.
- Gujjar…
- I need to pay her, bro. Come on.
Wait a sec. She owes you gas money too.
Fifty bucks for the gas.
I'm so sorry.
- Good morning, sir.
- Good morning.
He's sitting outside.
- Won't you try the--
- No!
- Good morning, Ranjeet.
- Good morning, Sharma ji.
- Come on, baby. Let's go.
- Come.
Go! Go and play.
- Good morning.
- Please come.
Ranjeet, how come seven officers
got transferred in Mumbai in one go?
Whose fault was it?
It was due to Pawar's foolishness.
He messed with the wrong guy.
- And who is replacing them?
- We will get to know by evening.
Don't worry. It happens sometimes.
I don't know.
I was thinking of getting
Gautam Jha into the team.
Gautam has no interest in Operations.
He has joined the Rewards team.
He says, he'll stay there till he retires.
- Where is Sajjad nowadays?
- Where else?
Like a moth is drawn to a flame,
he'll turn up.
Guys, we better explain clearly to him
not to blackmail movie stars passing
through the airport. He clings to them.
- Let's call Vincent.
- Yeah.
- Contact Shreelata too.
- Yes. Lucknow airport.
Bro, let's call Shreelata.
Should we call Awasthi?
As instructed by Prakash sir,
we started putting our team together.
We called officers like Shreelata Nayyar,
Vincent Joy, Sajjad Sheikh, K.P. Awasthi
from different corners
of India urgently to Mumbai.
All these officers
had one thing in common.
All of them were honest,
intelligent and incorruptible.
- Good morning, sir.
- Good morning.
- Sit down.
- Thank you, sir.
On our first day at work,
none of us had a clue
that we'd have to pay such a big price
for our honesty in the days to come.
Found anything?
- What is it?
- Good morning, ma'am.
Don't breathe down my neck. Move.
Sorry, ma'am.
I was told to buddy up with you.
What custom duty will you charge
a passenger who brings,
and declares two cartons of cigarettes?
Ma'am… Thirty, ma'am.
Wrong answer.
Awasthi, he needs to be trained.
Come on. Sit down.
- Stop this bag.
- Okay, ma'am.
What's in there?
Ma'am, there is shampoo, toiletries,
chocolates, some toys,
a mobile phone charger,
two watches and jewelry.
But, ma'am, that's not gold, it's steel…
Just a sec, ma'am.
It's stainless steel, ma'am.
- It's stainless steel?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Shall we let it go?
- Yes. We can let it go.
Come here.
- Are these bags yours?
- Yeah.
Grab your bags and come with me.
We need to check them.
Sure.
- Help her.
- Yes, ma'am.
Ma'am, what are these?
These are toys for my niece.
- Such big ones?
- Teddy bears are usually big.
That's true.
But you see ma'am, this one is Chanel.
It's worth a little more than 50 lakhs,
and the Black Sense Market is little less.
They're limited edition Bearbricks.
So, it's up to you now.
You wanna pay the duty
or shall I confiscate these
and take you to court?
Choice is yours.
I'll pay the duty.
- Jyoti.
- Yes, madam?
Take her with you.
- Thank you.
Ma'am?
These toys look so ordinary.
How did you know
that they're high value commodities?
Because internet wasn't made just for
TikTok, Reels and Instagram.
Do me a favor. Go left from here
and count all the washrooms and tell me.
- Okay, ma'am.
- Hello? Put that back.
- Yes, tell me.
- Will you come to the APIS room?
- Arjun, look at this passenger.
She's done 12 trips from Al Dirah
to Mumbai in the last six months.
And in the last three years…
London, Paris, Al Dirah…
She's been everywhere.
So? She might be from a wealthy family.
What made you doubt her?
Forget the girl.
Look at her flight details.
London, Kolkata, Mumbai.
Paris, Delhi, Mumbai.
Al Dirah, Pune, Mumbai.
From international to domestic
and then from that domestic to Mumbai.
But the domestic destination
is different every time.
Priya Khubchandani's travel history
was quite interesting.
There's a small loophole
in airlines operations.
Many planes are used
for international flights.
And then, the same planes fly domestic.
For example, Sitara's flight
comes from Al Dirah to Lucknow.
The smuggler's courier boards
the international flight with the gold.
And hides it in the toilet.
After landing at Lucknow,
the courier confidently exits the plane.
The passengers disembark
and plane is cleaned.
The new crew will come,
then the plane will head towards Mumbai,
and a courier gets on to the plane
and grabs the gold at the right moment.
Seat belt signs are now off. However
keep your seatbelts loosely fastened.
You may now use the washroom.
And exits the Mumbai domestic airport
without any checking.
There's no chance of getting caught.
Because who the hell will
smuggle goods on a domestic flight?
I'll look into it.
Gujjar's shrewd eyes
had caught this passenger,
Priya Khubchandani's travel pattern.
Excuse me, ma'am. Mumbai Customs.
- Where are you coming from?
- Al Dirah. Any problem, Officer?
- Do you have your boarding pass?
- Wait a sec.
One of my officers has noticed
your MO and travel pattern.
Subtitle translation by: Monika Saraf