- Do you have your boarding pass?
- Wait a sec.
Thank you.
One of my officers has noticed
your MO and travel pattern.
What were your travel dates?
That was your MO, not mine.
- Where are you putting up?
- Novotel.
I'll pick you up tonight.
Thank you, ma'am.
- I don't know much about that.
- That's the…
- See you guys.
- Bye. See you.
- Okay. Bye.
- See you, Priya.
- Bye.
- There it is.
- See you on the next flight.
Your cab's not coming.
- Excuse me?
- AIU.
Can you come with me for a sec?
Any problem? What happened, sir?
We've received intel that you're
carrying gold concealed on your body.
Don't worry.
I know Captain Kapoor
is making you do this.
Please come.
Let's sit comfortably and talk.
Why do you do this?
He…
is my fiancé.
We are planning to buy a flat
in Bombay after marriage.
But it isn't possible
with our salaries, so…
That's Rohini Kapoor.
Your fiancé… Captain Shubham Kapoor's
lawfully wedded wife.
She lives with their two kids
and a dog at Mall Road, Delhi.
You're the fourth air hostess
manipulated by Captain Kapoor
with a promise of marriage.
It happens.
Everyone gets screwed over in life.
Bastard!
Now?
I have an offer for you.
Carry on with what you are doing.
I just want to get that bastard.
PRIYA - ALL WELL, HAD DOZED OFF.
UP NOW. WILL SEE YOU SOON.
Done.
- Well, hello.
- Hi.
- Nice.
- Come in.
Blue looks really good on you, yeah.
- Really?
- Oh, really! How I missed you!
Me too!
There are five in here. Hide them well.
Done. I'll be right back.
Wrong timing.
- After three days.
- Damn!
Okay, you rest up. I'll be right back.
Hey, where are you going?
It's Bangkok, baby.
I'll see you.
- I'm gonna miss you.
- I'll miss you too.
- See you.
- Bye.
Hello, sir.
Sir, what's wrong? Any problem?
Whose bag is this?
Sir, that's my bag. What's the problem?
Come with me, please.
I've been going through this channel
for ten years. I've never been stopped.
What's the problem, sir?
What happened today?
Will you open this, please?
Sir, but can you tell me what's up?
Okay, I'll open it.
Sir, but you won't find a thing.
What are you looking for, sir?
Sir, a pilot's life is very boring.
We only have clothes and toiletries.
Nothing else, sir.
Sir, you won't find anything.
I'm a senior pilot, sir.
Why are you checking me?
Sir!
Sir, that's not what it looks like.
Sir, this is not mine.
Sir, I'm being set up. I'm not kidding.
This is not mine, sir.
Sir, people are jealous of me
in the company. I'm not kidding, sir.
These are not mine, sir.
I'm a very clean guy, sir. I'm…
Bitch.
Well done.
- Were you scared?
- No.
I knew you had my back.
Coffee's very nice. Isn't it?
The weather has suddenly changed.
You can come to the point, you know?
Priya, a gold smuggling racket
is going on in Al Dera.
We need to infiltrate it. You up for it?
You know I will.
That's why you didn't arrest me, right?
Priya, this is very dangerous.
Think twice.
If you refuse,
I'll understand.
And I promise,
they won't find a clue against you.
But give it a thought again, please.
I don't need to.
- I should be grateful.
- To whom?
I should be grateful to Captain Kapoor.
Thanks to him, we have Priya 2.0.
Aren't you underestimating yourself?
He's the man behind all the gold
that lands in India from Al Dera. Anna.
Anna is treated as god
in the villages of Kerala.
As he has helped
a lot of people get jobs here.
But nobody knows that
through his Manpower Consultancy,
Anna identifies the needy
and makes them his couriers.
This is Anna's right-hand guy, Suresh.
And this is Rahul.
Anna's nephew
and our means to infiltrate the gang.
Rahul frequently travels to Mumbai,
and he only flies Emirair.
We get his schedule
from our Advanced Passenger--
Wait a sec. Wait a sec.
He flies Emirair,
but I work for Fly Thai Airways.
Not anymore.
Excuse me, sir.
Would you like a complimentary upgrade?
There's a seat available.
Sure.
So, that's your seat.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Sir, would you like to have something?
Thank you.
- Hello, sir.
- Oh, hi.
Hi. How've you been?
Good.
There's a complimentary--
Upgrade.
- Sir.
- Thank you.
Hi, sir.
- Sir.
- Thank you.
I'll just be back.
Excuse me.
Sorry, sir. But, I'm engaged.
That shouldn't be a problem for a dinner.
Next time you are in Al Dera, call me.
Let me host you this time.
Sure.
Obviously the issue was at our end, right?
We didn't communicate at all. Just a sec.
- Hello?
- Hi.
Hi. Who is this?
This is Priya. Remember me?
Just a sec.
You didn't tell me what exactly do you do?
I run a global export business.
Wow!
Nothing great about it.
We're just making some money.
Really? Sounds interesting to me.
Ten kilos of gold strapped to her body.
And she went through the green channel.
She had it strapped everywhere
on her body.
You should've seen her face.
Unbelievable! I mean… And you know what?
It was her third trip in six months.
Not a clue about smuggling
and wanted to be a popat.
Popat means… courier.
You know a lot about smuggling.
Not just smuggling,
Mumbai International Airport,
customs officers,
helpers, loaders,
I know about them all.
All those ready to take the plunge,
I know it all.
Priya!
- All okay?
- Sorry.
- It's nothing. No.
- Hey, why are you crying?
They're firing me.
- For unruly behavior.
- What?
Tell me, do you find me unruly?
No, no, not at all.
And ever since Amit heard about this,
he called off the engagement.
Listen, stop crying. Stop crying.
I'm there for you. I'll sort it out.
Trust me, I'll make it all right.
Welcome. May I?
- Good morning, sir.
- Good morning.
Priya, I told you about Anna, right?
This is Anna.
My mom, my dad, my boss. He is my world.
Hello.
And this is the vice-captain of our team,
Suresh kaka.
Priya.
- Anna, shall I show her the office?
- Sure, go ahead.
Come.
What happened?
No, nothing.
- Hi.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Which way to the coffee shop? Thanks.
- This way, ma'am.
All good?
Yeah. All well.
Two guys have been following me
from the airport.
One is sitting in the lobby trying hard
to read a newspaper and the other one
is smoking in front of the main gate.
Let's go.
I found this list
in a file at Anna's office.
It has the names of those officers
who are confirmed to be working for Anna.
- When did Patel join them?
- It's been three months.
Take a look. Suresh has devised
two new methods of concealing the gold.
First, concealing it in suitcases.
One can carry 5.5 kilos of gold
in check-in bag and 3.5 in a carry-on bag.
These guys are very intelligent.
The second one?
I told you about those chemists.
They have invented a chemical process
by which they
can convert gold bars into powder.
This powder looks exactly like
Oranix powder,
and it can't be detected by scanners.
They bring it here
and convert it back into bars.
I've handed over one-kilo boxes
to five couriers myself.
And they faced no issues.
Is there any talk about new officers?
It's a wait and watch situation.
Anyway, they smuggle goods only when
their officers are on duty.
What is it? What are you thinking?
I'm thinking
how to crack down hard on them.
I have an idea.
But Priya, you will have to leave
Al Dera after that.
If I leave Al Dera,
where will I work?
And where will I stay?
Exactly what I was thinking.
Where will you stay?
Okay, when is your flight?
Soon. In two hours.
What's happening here?
- Hey, hurry up! Move away!
- Two minutes. I'm working on it.
What's going on? Sergio, go and check.
Hey, lady! What are you doing, huh?
- It's all yours.
- Good job.
Rob!
Thank you.
- Hello?
- Good morning, sir.
The packet has been secured.
Good. Value?
Four hundred crore plus.
Had to give two to the local gang.
- How long will distribution take?
- Close to three weeks.
I'll send the flight details by tomorrow.
Okay.
Luke.
- Is he the one who committed the theft?
- He wanted to get married. He was in Rome.
Don't kill me.
Please.
Come in.
- Sir.
- Arjun.
Come. Take a seat.
I have some good news.
The World Customs Conference is being
held in Mumbai on the 24th of this month.
Good news is that you and your team
will be responsible
for managing the guest protocol.
Sir, you brought us back
to curb smuggling.
If we'll be serving delegates…
Shift details and new roster for officer
duties will reach syndicate by evening.
When they get to know that all former
officers are on duty at the airport,
they will think that the channels
are open for them all day long.
Brilliant.
Yes, sir.
Okay. I'll send it over to you.
- Hey, man! Watch it!
- Oh, Patel sir. Sorry. I was distracted.
- Sorry.
- Congrats on getting reinstated, Meena.
What good is this reinstatement,
Patel sahib?
My entire batch has been assigned
to serve the delegates.
Did we join Customs to catch smugglers
or serve these foreigners?
Yeah.
I saw it in the duty roster.
But why are you complaining?
Have fun in the 5-star hotel for five days
and then you can catch the smugglers.
It's not like smuggling is going to
stop at this airport, right? Shake on it.
I think the piece goes here. Right?
- Nerissa!
- Yes, sir?
Oh, hi!
What are you playing? Can I join you?
Yes, Patel.
- Hello, sir. Good news for you.
- What is it?
Mumbai airport will be ours
for the taking on the 24th.
Who told you about this?
Suresh kaka, have you forgotten,
I used to be an air hostess?
I still have contacts at the airport.
I haven't forgotten anything.
But your proposal is very risky.
Suresh!
Namaskar, Choudhary sahib.
- How are you, Anna?
- All well.
Mumbai airport will be on holiday on 24th.
Get the maximum stuff ready.
Twenty men won't be enough for Junior.
- Send some from Al Dera.
- It will be done, sahib.
I'm sending three watches, worth 50 crore.
They need to reach Mumbai.
How will you do it?
My network of captains
will take care of it, Choudhary sahib.
Great.
Okay, Choudhary sahib.
Satisfied now?
The chick's intel is correct.
So, what's your plan?
First, we will take 20 kilos of gold
on these nine domestic flights.
That's 180 kilos. 320 kilos is left.
Twenty kilos gold for a single person?
It is risky.
Two people can carry ten kilos each
on the domestic flight.
Yes.
- How many passengers do you have?
- Sixty-one.
Good. Sixty-one.
I'll manage with 41.
You can assign
the remaining 20 to Ethiopia.
Give me the details and backgrounds
of these 61 passengers.
I'll send the heavily-built ones
to Ethiopia.
And keep the rest for myself.
Fine.
Here's the list.
One passenger can carry nine kilos of gold
using two suitcases.
Thirty-two times nine is 288.
And we haven't even used
the Oranix powder yet.
How much powder do we have?
About 30-32 kilos.
Perfect. That does it.
These passengers will carry a kilo of
Oranix powder alongwith the suitcases.
Great. Let's do this then.
There are 2,500 chips, Vijay bhai.
How will you do it?
Look, madam.
There are 60 instrument boxes.
Apart from that,
we have sound and light SKP boxes.
Everything will fit in those easily.
Don't worry.
We just need somebody to manage the heavy
luggage at the airport counter. That's it.
I'll take care of that. How many people
are there in the bhangra troupe?
Thirty dancers
and eight support staff members.
You'll be able to send 50 luxury suitcases
and 20 high-end purses through them?
Easily, madam. Don't you worry.
Leave it to me.
Okay.
I've taken this huge financial risk
based solely on your trust.
Don't worry, Arbab. The consignment
will land in Mumbai in two days.
The account will be settled within a week.
Yes, we are on time. All right!
Blurt out what's bothering you.
Or else it'll keep hurting.
Such a big consignment is being sent
in one go. If something goes haywire…
I spoke to Patel. The intel is solid.
Our men are on duty. There's no risk.
Priya's entry into our business like this
kind of bothers me.
What do you want to do about it?
Good evening, sir.
- Get me a double.
- Sure.
Come over, Arjun.
I just got a tip.
Choudhary Syndicate is planning
to land 500 kilos of yellow on the 24th.
- We have to get them.
- But how?
We are not going to be
on counter duty that day.
That's only on paper. Prakash sir
will change the roster at the last minute.
Okay.
Don't mess with small-time couriers
for the next few days.
I want their confidence to grow.
- Manoj.
- Please come, sir.
- Have you booked your ticket?
- Yes, I'll send you my boarding pass.
Don't worry about me.
Priya, you have to leave
before the first contraband flight
takes off, got it?
I've sent you two lists.
The first list has details of 52 people.
Twenty will come from Ethiopia
and 32 from Al Dera.
The second list
carries names of nine people
and 18 seat numbers
where packets are hidden.
But these nine people
will leave for their destinations
after leaving the packages at their seats.
Then, 18 new couriers will board
those domestic converted flights
and each one of them will carry a package
and exit as soon as the plane lands.
Good. I'll meet you directly in Mumbai.
- You take care.
- I will. Bye.
- Hi.
- Hello, madam.
- Are you going out?
- No. I was thinking of hitting the gym.
You know I haven't gone for three days.
And last night,
I had so many desserts, so--
Forget it. Anna has called
for an urgent meeting. We have to go.
You could've just called me.
I'd have come directly.
But then I would've missed
the chance to go on long drive with you.
Let's go.
Just a sec. I'll get my bag.
Shall we?
Let's go.
Anna and Choudhary sahib
are very happy with your work.
Anna was saying
that a big bonus awaits you this time.
- Can I ask you something?
- Yes.
International flights
are converted to domestic flights,
was this your own idea
or somebody else told you?
Who will tell me, Rahul?
Some customs officer might have told you.
You think I work for Customs?
Not me, Suresh kaka thinks so.
That's why he's
given me the responsibility
of keeping an eye on you
till the consignment lands.
Don't open the door.
Yes, Rahul. Tell me.
Hello, Anna. Cops have surrounded us.
- What? Why?
- I don't know.
- Come out of the car.
- Come out of the car, madam
Why you stop me, officer?
Hello, Rahul?
Step out of the car, quickly!
Come out.
Come out of the car!
Stop right here.
Move faster, move.
Check the car.
What do you want? Why have you stopped us?
This is not ours.
- Sir, sir. This is not my car, sir.
- Officer!
Carry her out. Take it with you.
There is a misunderstanding, Officer.
- Rahul, tell them! This is not my car!
- Take her with you and take him away.
- Take her with you, and take him away.
- Please try to understand, officer!
Please try to understand.
This is not ours.
Get in the car!
- Let me make a call. Let me…
- We will talk, get in the car.
Rahul.
There is a misunderstanding.
Will somebody listen to me?
Please let me…
Subtitle translation by: Sanjay Malhotra