Please let me go.
Please, please. Let me go. Please.
Let me go. Please don't. Don't.
Don't kill me. No, no, no.
No. Please, don't kill me.
Don't kill me. Please. Please!
No, no, no. No!
- What's going on here?
- Jai Hind, sir.
Is there a criminal here
that you're guarding?
Get moving.
- Out!
- Okay, sir.
- Vincent, Sajjad, Kumar sir is here.
- Okay.
Whose team are you working for?
A custodial death, a potential witness
is killed in a shootout, all in one day?
What is going on?
Sir, I take full responsibility for this.
It is all on you.
And you?
What happened there? Speak up.
Sir… when we reached
Ramesh bhai's house…
Hey! Who are you? How did you get in?
Sir, what are you doing?
The gun could go off.
- I'll kill you. Don't come near.
- Sir, the gun could go off.
- Get back. Get back!
- Sir, you might shoot someone.
Drop the gun, sir. Let go, sir.
Sir? Sir?
Why did you have to play the hero?
The DRI team was already there. Then?
Sir, Commissioner sahib wants to see you.
Who was interrogating Mukim?
Sir, we had exercised full caution.
This is Aslam's doing.
- Send me a detailed report.
- Okay, sir.
Take his statement right now.
Arjun.
- This new guy, what's his name?
- Kulveer Dhuria.
This idiot will get arrested, prosecuted.
Sir, we have to protect him.
I mean, you have to protect him, sir.
- Did you make a DRI-1 of this raid?
- It's on your desk, sir.
Suspend the entire team. Immediately.
- No, sir.
- What?
Just three months
are left for my retirement.
Let me spend my time peacefully!
Do what you want after I've gone.
Not a single member of my team
will be suspended, sir.
I'm transferring them to the back office.
You can initiate
an internal enquiry if you wish.
Allot a six-month time frame.
Because that will be enough for me
to wipe out this syndicate.
Really?
Choudhary has bailed out Aslam.
And Ramesh bhai is dead.
That is my lookout, sir.
My team will not be suspended.
And in return, the way you set me up
in Bangkok will stay within this room.
Rahul almost died because of them,
Choudhary sahib.
Our business runs on fear.
Once fear is gone, business is over.
Listen to me. Take out a couple
and the rest will straighten up.
Rizaura?
Sir, we have taken a big hit.
But I totally disagree
with what Anna is proposing.
We win some and we lose some.
Violence is not a solution.
Hey, what are you talking--
Sorry, but that's what I feel.
I am in agreement with Anna. Let's get rid
of a few guys from their team.
- Junior?
- Yes. boss.
I can't let my couriers suffer.
- If word gets out, then we are done here.
- Totally.
Rahul?
Choudhary sahib,
we have to underline our presence here.
If we don't retaliate,
they'll completely get out of hand.
Sharma ji, call Raghu.
Choudhary sahib.
Yes, Suresh.
There's a middle path.
Want to hear me out?
Hello.
Hello, Arjun Meena. Bada Choudhary here.
Hello?
Relax.
Your heart is racing.
Had I called, it would've been yours.
Why did you call?
I have a tip and some advice for you.
The tip is that two of my men
are traveling on EK535 tomorrow,
each carrying 25 kilos of gold
and they will land at your airport.
Their names are
Sushil Verma and Atul Rathod.
And my advice is that you won't stop them.
Rather, you'll let them exit safely.
Why would I take your advice, Choudhary?
Because one should listen to elders,
Arjun. It's part of our culture.
- Mom?
- Yes?
- I'm going to win at the Sports Day.
- Okay.
I run so fast
that everyone will be stunned.
Hand it over.
Let's go.
- Shall I show you how I run?
- Yes, okay.
Mom. Mom! Mom, I won! I won!
- Mitali madam!
- Yes?
A small gift for you from Choudhary sahib.
- Jiya!
- Oh, no!
- Mom!
- Jiya!
Momma, I can't see.
Give me the gun.
How are you, sahib?
What, sahib? You seize a lot of our stuff.
Stop bringing it in, I'll stop seizing.
You'll land in a big mess someday.
Use your brain a little.
Got it?
A petty goon like you
will explain it to me?
You're a big gangster now?
Choudhary sahib
has sent a special gift for you.
What happened?
Mom! Mom! I won! I won!
A gift from Choudhary sahib.
- Mom! Mom!
- Jiya!
- Mom!
- Nothing happened. Nothing happened.
- Just a second. Just a second.
- Madam!
It was just chili water this time.
Mend your ways.
Or it'll be acid next time. Let's go.
Baby, listen to me.
Look at me, baby. Look at me.
Nothing happened. It was just water.
Are you okay?
A special gift for you
from Choudhary sahib.
How did you like our demo, Gujjar sahib?
It'll be real bullets next time.
Mend your ways. Asshole!
And they all got calls too. Vincent?
They described
my dad's entire routine with timings.
They've warned me
that if I try to be too duty-driven…
In front of the church, my dad will be…
They called me too and said
that the blue shirt
was better than the one I wore today.
They've threatened me too.
Not to get swayed by seniors.
I got a threat call on the landline, sir.
By chance, my wife picked it up.
She is still howling.
She hasn't stopped, sir.
Sir!
I was walking on the car, sir.
And a red colored road swerved past me.
- Hello?
- We spared you this time, bloody Sajjad!
If you stop Choudhary sahib's courier
ever at the airport,
we'll run you over with this car. Got it?
I have two little kids, sir.
Vincent, take Sajjad.
- Get him changed. Come on.
- Sir.
Let's go.
If I wanted to be shot,
I'd have joined the army, man.
Relax. Relax. Come on.
- Mitali.
- Yes, sir?
You want to take Jiya for counseling?
No need, sir.
She is a tough kid. She'll handle it.
Sir, since everybody is here, so…
I have a recording.
I have a tip and some advice for you.
The tip is that two of my men
are traveling on EK535 tomorrow,
each carrying 25 kilos of gold
and they will land at your airport.
Their names are
Sushil Verma and Atul Rathod.
And the advice is that
you won't stop them.
Rather, you will let them exit safely.
It's about to land in half an hour.
I'll catch them both
and take them to the police--
Gujjar, don't be stupid.
- It's not just about you.
- Thank… Thank you, sir.
No, I mean I am grateful
that you think like this.
- He is right.
- Arjun.
Sir, we should let them go today.
Today Choudhary has the upper hand.
We are not ready for today's war.
Let's live to fight another day.
Agreed.
Let's lie low today.
Let Choudhary
have the delusion of a victory.
Look, there he is.
He is not going to do anything.
No, he knows it.
Let's drop the bag and get going.
Come on, bhai. Put it on the belt quick.
Did you see their faces?
They were scared to the bone.
Choudhary sir's terror is such, bhai.
They have to be scared.
Hurry up, man. Give the bag. Give it.
They're just taking it all in.
None could've stopped us.
Grab the bag.
Bloody hell!
You fucker!
Get him! Hold him!
Let go!
Come on.
Take a good look at these smugglers!
They were bringing gold into India.
This will be the fate of every smuggler.
- Move!
- Wow!
This is called integrity.
No government officer
has the guts to do this nowadays.
They were bringing gold into India.
This will be the fate of every smuggler.
Move!
Ranjeet, it's Arbab.
Salaam alaikum, Arbab.
Waliakum-asalaam.
Fifty kilos of gold was seized
again yesterday, Choudhary sahib.
I was sure it would go through.
But it didn't.
Omar sahib wants to see you
as soon as possible.
I'll get back to you.
You didn't get me.
Omar sahib wants
to meet you here at the earliest.
I'll take the morning flight.
Thank you.
- Sorry, man.
- Don't mess with me.
I had told you to control yourself.
Let go today, grab them tomorrow.
Now we all are on Choudhary's radar.
You shouldn't have interfered.
I was handling it.
Hey, Iron Man! Had I not been there,
he would have beaten the hell out of you.
Beaten the hell, my foot!
What is it now? Why are you crying?
Nothing.
Will you just tell me what's wrong?
I got a call from dad today.
He'd seen the video.
You know what he said?
He called me a complete idiot.
My own father calls me an idiot
because I didn't sell my integrity.
What a bullshit world this is!
What kind of father,
what kind of family, what kind of society,
calls an honest person an idiot?
You know…
This is a weak society, Gujjar.
Honest people like you
are in the minority in this society.
That's why.
I'm proud of you guys.
Never change.
You are setting an example
for generations to come.
So, always trust yourself
and your attitude.
It's okay.
Thank you, sir.
But the video has gone viral.
All the way to Delhi.
Here we are, your home sweet home.
Listen.
It's your turn to pick me up tomorrow.
Will do.
See you.
I called off my engagement.
Why?
Did he turn out to be honest too?
No.
He's corrupt and that's what
he'll be his entire life.
I saw you thrashing those smugglers today,
I realized both the value
and significance of integrity.
I won't be able to afford
your dream lifestyle, Meenakshi.
I am human, Ravi.
I'm sorry.
I shared everything with you.
- Personal, professional, and--
- I'm really sorry.
- Let's go home.
- No.
I don't deserve you.
Don't sit here. Come on.
I will come.
I will come back to you the day
you forgive me completely.
I really love you, Ravi.
You never took so long to answer.
It's okay.
Hello?
Arjun Meena.
I gave you some advice yesterday.
I didn't like your advice, Choudhary.
So I didn't take it.
I know. So listen to this now.
If they're ringing my doorbell,
tell your men to wait there.
I'm coming upstairs.
The doorbell is being rung
at Apartment 2/56, Seva Sadan.
And you very well know
who lives at that address.
Let go, fucker! Let go!
Hey! Hey!
Gujjar! Gujjar!
Gujjar!
Please send the raid profile
by the evening to sir and me.
Sir.
Search warrant, sir.
- Yeah. You can start.
- Okay, get going.
It's a search warrant for the house.
Yeah. For the house.
Let's go.
They found 50 lakhs
in cash in the kitchen.
We both know what's happening.
- Chouhan?
- Yes, sir.
- Did you inform the family?
- Yes.
My child.
What happened to Ravinder?
He was fine. What happened?
Come on. I need a ride.
- Take a left ahead.
- Okay, sir.
Right into that compound.
Get down.
Why are we here, sir?
- How much did you get for killing Ramesh?
- Sir?
- Hey?
- Speak up!
- What's happening?
One crore, sir. Sir, please listen to me.
- Who are you?
- Superintendent Arjun Meena.
Where is the Senior PI's cabin?
- This way.
- Move.
Please listen to me.
Please, sir.
Please listen to me once, sir.
Come in.
Superintendent Arjun Meena
from Mumbai Customs, sir.
This kid wants to give a confession.
- Sit down.
- Sir.
And start talking. Come on!
I got a call an hour before
we were to leave for the raid.
Hello?
Just answer in yes or no.
Do you want to earn one crore?
Our man will meet you
at the Starbucks outside.
He will give you 50 lakh rupees and a gun.
Your team is going to raid
Ramesh bhai's house at 10:30 am sharp.
But you won't find Ramesh bhai there.
There is a prayer room in his house.
A sculpture is hung
on the wall of that room.
There is a cavity room behind that idol.
That's where you'll find Ramesh bhai.
Kill him.
The remaining 50 lakhs
will be at your home in the evening.
There's nothing here. Come on.
Who the hell are you? How'd you get in?
I've been sent for your safety,
Ramesh bhai.
Please sit, I'll check.
Please sit, sir. I'm here.
Hey! What's that?
You bloody--
Sir! Sir!
You killed a man for money? Bastard!
He was a criminal, sir.
An enemy of the nation and society.
I was getting one crore, so I did it, sir.
It was a mistake, sir. Please forgive me.
- Constable!
- Forgive me.
It was a mistake. Please forgive me ,sir.
Sir, forgive me. Sir.
Arjun, I'm a little confused.
You are at the Gamdevi police station.
And my men are just leaving.
Priya is in one of your safe houses,
so in this insane Mumbai traffic,
who will get to her faster?
You… or my men?
Subtitle translation by: Monika Saraf